Guide to the Wilfrid S. Sellars Papers, 1899-1990 ASP.1991.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Research and Writing, 1925-1990; II.
  - Manuscripts of Other Authors, 1925-1990; 3.
    - Flo, Olav, "Bibliography of the Philosophical Writings of Georg Hendrik von Wright, 1938-1966" (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Fogelin, Robert J.
      - "Inferential Constructions", c. 1964 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - "When I Look at a Tomato There is Much I Cannot See", 1980 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Ford, Daniel
      - "An Introduction to Sellarsian Epistemology: The Attack on the Myth of the Given", 1969 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - "The Myth of Natural Kinds", 1970 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Freundlich, Yehudah, "Phenomenalism and Representative Realism Combined: A Theory of Perception", 1972 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Friedman, Stephen, "Ultimate Homogeneity: A Dialog", 1984 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Gale, Richard
      - "Comments on Davidson's 'Adverbial Modification" (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - "Could Logical Space Be Empty?", undated (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - "Critical Study of Studies in Metaphilosophy", undated (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - "Do Performative Utterances have any Constative Function?", undated (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - "Endorsing Predications", 1961 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - "The Fictive Use of Language", undated (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - "The Generality of Predications", undated (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - "Goodman and Fakes", undated (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - "Has the Present any Duration?", undated (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - "'Here' and 'Now'", undated (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - "Here and There, Now and Then: Disanalogies between Space and Time", 1980 (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - "Is It Now Now?', undated (Box 61, Folder 19)
      - "The Language of Time", undated (Box 61, Folder 20)
      - "McTaggart on the Relation between the A-Series and the B-Series", undated (Box 61, Folder 21)
      - "Negation, Non-Being, and Real Possibility", undated (Box 61, Folder 22)
      - "On the Concept of Being Present", undated (Box 61, Folder 23)
      - "On What There Isn't", undated (Box 61, Folder 24)
      - "Ostensive Definitions of Time", undated (Box 61, Folder 25)
      - "Propositions and Propositional Acts" (Box 61, Folder 26)
      - "Propositions, Judgments, Sentences and Statements", undated (Box 61, Folder 27)
      - "Pure and Impure Descriptions', undated (Box 61, Folder 28)
      - Review of Space and Time, undated (Box 61, Folder 29)
      - "Strawson's Restricted Theory of Referring", undated (Box 61, Folder 30)
      - "Tense and Presuppositions", undated (Box 61, Folder 31)
      - "Tensed Statements", undated (Box 61, Folder 32)
      - "William James and the Ethics of Belief", undated (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - Gallagher, Neil, Untitled, undated (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Garson, James, "Here and Now", 1968 (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Garver, Newton
      - "Rules", undated (Box 61, Folder 36)
      - "Subject and Predicate", undated (Box 61, Folder 37)
      - "Varieties of Use and Motion", 1963 (Box 61, Folder 38)
    - Gauker, Christopher
      - "Conditionals and Assertibility", 1985 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - "Conditionals in Context", 1985 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - "Foder's Theory of Propositional Attitudes", 1982 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - "Language as Tool", 1984 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - "Mind and Chance", 1984 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - "Objective Interpretationism", 1986 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - "Principle of Charity", 1984 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - "Sellars Versus Van Fraassen on Scientific Realism", 1981 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - "Semantics without Reference", 1983 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - "Thought as Inner Speech", 1985 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Gaus Gerald, "Anarchism and Political Philosophy", 1977 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Gendlin, E. T., "Two Phrenologists Do Not Disagree", 1976 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Gewirth, Alan, "Some Conceptual Issues in the Relation Between Law and Morality", 1967 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Gibbard, Allan, "Contingent Identity", undated (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Gibson, James J., "Perception as a Function of Stimulation", 1955 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Giere, Ronald, "On the Metaphilosophy of Science", undated (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Gill, John G., "Abstract Definition of the Good", 1969 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Ginet, Carl, "Might We Have No Choice?", undated (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Glidden, David, "Aristotelian Aesthesis and the Hellenistic Problem of Representation", undated (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Gold, Jeffrey, "Ambiguity of Name in Plato's Cratylus", 1976 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Goldman, Alvin
      - "Discrimination and Perceptual Knowledge", 1972 (Box 62, Folder 21)
      - "Relation Between Epistemology and Psychology", 1981 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Goldstein, Lawrence
      - "Adverbial Theory of Conceptual Thought", 1981 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - "Scientific Scotism - The Emperor's New Trousers or has Armstrong Made Some Real Strides?", 1981 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Good, I. J., "Errata and Appenda to Publications by I. J. Good", 1978 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Gordon, Roy
      - "Meinongian Semantics Problems with Emendations to Evaluation of", 1974 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Review of Film Language: A Semiotics of the Cinema, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Gould, Carol C., "Ontological Foundations of Democracy", 1979 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Grant, Edward, "Place and Space in Medieval Physical Thought", undated (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Greenspan, P.S., "Danto and Others on Agent Causation, Volitions, and the Humean Self", 1975 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Grice, H. P., "Utterers Meaning Sentence Meaning and Word Meaning", undated (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Griffiths, A. Phillips, "Transcendental Arguments", undated (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Grossmann, Reinhardt, "Perceptual Objects Elementary Particles and Emergent Properties", 1970 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Grover, Dorothy
      - "Propositional Quantifiers", 1970 (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - "Truth", 1983 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Grunbaum, Adolf
      - "Absolute and Relational Theories of Space and Space Time", 1974 (Box 63, Folder 14)
      - "Ad Hoc Auxiliary Hypotheses and Falsificationism", 1976 (Box 63, Folder 15)
      - "Auto-Predictability and Freedom of Action in a Deterministic Universe", undated (Box 63, Folder 16)
      - "Can Psychoanalytic Theory be Cogently Tested On the Couch?", 1981 (Box 63, Folder 17)
      - "Can We Ascertain the Falsity of a Scientific Hypothesis?", 1969 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - "Carnap's Views on the Foundation of Geometry", 1958 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - "Clarification of the Critique of Reichenbach's Attempt to Physicize the Event", undated (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - "Comments on Professor Roger Bucks Paper Reflexive Predications", 1962 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - "Conventionalism in Geometry", 1958 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - "Critique of the Philosophical Legacy of Pierre Duhem", 1964 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - "Duhemian Argument", 1959 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - "Free Will and Laws of Human Behavior", 1969 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - "Geometry Chronometry and Empiricism", 1959 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - "Geometry of the Rotating Disk in the Special Theory of Relativity", 1976 (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - "Introduction to the Symposium on Graves", 1972 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - "Is Pre Acceleration of Particles in Diracs Electrodynamics", 1974 (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - "Is a Universal Nocturnal Expansion Falsificable or Physically Vacuous?", undated (Box 64, Folder 13)
      - "Logical Foundations of Psychoanalytic Theory", 1982 (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - "Nature of Time", 1962 (Box 64, Folder 15)
      - "On the Origins of Relativity Theory Remarks on Professor Holtons Essay", 1960 (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - "Ontology of the Curvature of Empty Space in the Geometrodynamics", 1972 (Box 64, Folder 17)
      - "Philosophy 263: Philosophy of Physics and Mathematics", 1955 (Box 64, Folder 18)
      - "Popper on Irreversibility", 1962 (Box 64, Folder 19)
      - "Professor Dingle on Falsifiability A Second Rejoinder", 1960 (Box 64, Folder 20)
      - "Question on Popper from Adolf Grunbaum", 1974 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - "Relativity of Simultaneity Within a Single Galilean Frame: A Rejoinder", undated (Oversize 198)
      - "Reply to Christensen", 1971 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - "Reply to Hilary Putnam's An Examination of Grunbaum's Philosophy of Science", 1968 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Review of Concepts of Space, 1956 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Review of Current Issues in the Philosophy of Science, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - "Role of A Priori Elements in Physical Theory", 1959 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - "Scientific Assertibility of Statements about the Past and about the Future", 1963 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - "Some Comments on Operationism", 1953 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - "Space", c. 1962 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - "The Special Theory of Relativity as a Case Study of the Importance of the Philosophy of Science for the History of Science", 1962 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - "The Status of Temporal Becoming", c. 1964 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - "The Structure of Science", c. 1962 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - "Temporally-Asymmetric Principles Parity Between Explanation and Prediction, and Mechanism versus Teleology", 1961 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Gulessarian, Theodore,"The Defensibility of the Identity Theory and Eliminative Materialism", c. 1968 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Gupta, Anil
      - "The Logic of Common Nouns", 1977 (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - "Remarks on Definitions and the Concept of Truth", 1989 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Gutting, Gary
      - "Action and Freedom", 1976 (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - "Critical Review: Wilfrid Sellars, Essays in Philosophy and Its History", 1975 (Box 65, Folder 18)
      - "Scientific Realism", c. 1977 (Box 65, Folder 19)
      - "Scientific Realism vs. Constructive Empiricism", 1981 (Box 65, Folder 20)
      - "Sellars' Philosophy of Science", 1973 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Guyer, Paul
      - "Complexity or Contradiction: A Problem in Kant's Theory of Aesthetic Pleasure", 1975 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - "Disinterestedness and Desire in Kant's Aesthetics", c. 1977 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - "From Objectivity to Intersubjectivity: A Reading of the Critique of Judgment", 1972 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - "Interest, Nature, and Art: A Problem in Kant's Aesthetics", 1977 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Kant and the Claims of Taste, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 5-7)
      - "Locke's Problem with Real Species", c. 1961 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - "Predication and Contradiction", 1975 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - "A Problem in Kant's Account of Disinterestedness", 1977 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Haack, R.J., "Quine's Theory of Logic", 1977 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Haack, Susan
      - "Coherentism Discomposed", 1989 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Review of Epistemic Responsibility, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - "Epistemologically Relevant Sociology of Science", 1982 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - "Evidence against Reliabilism", 1989 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - "Know is just a Four-Letter Word", 1983 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - "Realism", 1985 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - "Rebuilding the Ship while Sailing on the Water", 1989 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - "Recent Obituaries of Epistemology", 1988 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Review of Rationality, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - "Scholastic Realist of a Somewhat Extreme Stripe", 1989 (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - "Surprising Noises Rorty and Hesse on Metaphor", 1987 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - "Two Faces of Quine's Naturalism", 1990 (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - "What is the Problem of the Empirical Basis", 1985 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Haggstrom, Warren
      - "Foundations of Language and Logic", undated (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - "History of Ancient Western Logic and Some Remarks Concerning Other Periods", undated (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - "Logic of Leibniz", c.1951 (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - "Some Preliminary Informal Remarks Concerning Value Logic", 1951 (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - "There are Synthetic A Priori Judgments", undated (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - "Western Definition and Eastern Laksana", 1952 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Hahm, David
      - "Hellenistic Theories of Vision and Color Perception", 1965 (Box 67, Folder 21)
      - "Weight and Natural Motions Aristotle and his Predecessors", 1959 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Halcomb, Jay C., "Nominalism and Realism", 1985 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Hall, Everett
      - "Ethics for Today", undated (Box 67, Folder 24)
      - "History of Ideas", undated (Box 67, Folder 25)
      - "Is Philosophy a Science", undated (Box 67, Folder 26)
      - Review of Readings in Ethical Theory, 1952 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Hamblin, C. L., "Starting and Stopping", 1968 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Hammond, Kenneth, "Representative vs. Systematic Design in Clinical Psychology", 1951 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Hankins, Thomas, "Algebra as Pure Time William Rowan Hamilton and the Foundations of Algebra", 1969 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Hanson, Norwood Russell
      - "Anatomy of Discovery", 1967 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - "Budget of Cross Type Inferences", 1959 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 9 on the philosophical aspects of microphysics, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - "Classical Particle Physics", 1955 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - "Contra Equivalence", undated (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - "Copernican Disturbance and the Keplerian Revolution", 1950 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - "Five Cautions for the Copenhagen Interpretations Critics", 1957 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - "Good Inductive Reasons", undated (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - "Hypotheses Fingo", 1967 (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - "Logical Positivism and the Interpretation of Scientific Theories", 1967 (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - "Mathematical Power of Epicyclical Astronomy", undated (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - "Mere Predictability", undated (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - "Poverty of Agnosticism", 1961 (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - "Sellars on Theories", undated (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - "Some Philosophical Aspects of Contemporary Cosmologies", 1952 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - "What I don't Believe", undated (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Hare, R. M., "The Bearing of Ethics on Moral Decisions", 1958 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Harman, Gilbert
      - "Comments on Donald Davidson's Paper, 'How is Weakness of the Will Possible'", 1967 (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - "Moral Relativism Defended", 1973 (Box 68, Folder 22)
      - "Practical Reasoning", 1974 (Box 68, Folder 23)
      - Review of Science and Metaphysics, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Harnish, Robert M., "Reliable Solipsism?", 1980 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Harper, William
      - "Conceptual Change, Incommensurability and Special Relativity Kinematics", 1978 (Box 68, Folder 26)
      - "Kant's Empirical Realism and the Second Analogy of Experience", 1978 (Box 68, Folder 27)
      - "Rational Belief Change Popper Functions and Counterfactuals", 1974 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - "Rational Conceptual Change", c. 1977 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - "Space and Kant's Empirical Realism", 1982 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Hart, H. L. A.
      - "Ascription of Responsibility and Rights", 1949? (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - "Legal Responsibility and Excuses", 1953 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Haugeland, John
      - Alphabetical systems and systematization, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - "Heidegger on Being a Person", 1981 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - "Hume on Personal Identity", 1979 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - "Mother of Intention", 1980 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - "The Nature and Plausibility of Cognitivism", c. 1977 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - "Programs, Causal Powers, and Intentionality", 1980 (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - "Semantic Engines An Introduction to Mind Design", c.1979 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - "Weak Supervenience", 1980 (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - "What is it to be True?", 1973 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Hausman, Alan, "Non-Euclidean Geometry and Relative Consistency Proofs", 1969 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Hausman, Carl, "Value and the Peircean Categories", 1967 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Heelan, Patrick
      - "Complementarity, Context Dependence and Quantum Logic", 1969 (Box 69, Folder 17)
      - "Luneberg and the Visual Interpretation of Physical Space", 1968 (Box 69, Folder 18)
      - "Quantum Logic and Classical Logic Their Respective Roles", 1969 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Heidelberger, Herbert, "Certainty and Probality", 1962 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Herman, Glen, "Types and Categories", 1978 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Helmer, Olaf, "On the Epistemology of the Inexact Sciences", 1958 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Hempel, Carl, "Implications of Carnap's Work for the Philosophy of Science", 1954 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Herbst, Peter
      - "Fact, Form, and Intentionality", 1968 (Box 69, Folder 24)
      - "Names and Identities and Beginnings and Ends", 1972 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Hesse, Mary, "Consilience of Inductions", 1965 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Hetherington, Stephen
      - "Alston and Epistemic Foundationalism", 1986 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - "Gettier Something You Thought You Knew about Knowledge', 1987 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Hick, John H., "On the Verification of Religious Statements', c.1987 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Hiebert, Erwin N., "An Appraisal of the Work of Ernst Mach Scientist Historian Philosopher", 1971 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Hill, E. L., "Particles and Fields in Modern Physics", 1962 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Hillman, Donald J., "Time", undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Hinshaw, Virgil G., Jr.
      - "Russell's Realism", 1942 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - "Eight Dialectical Patterns Controlling the Philosophical Use of 'Exist'", 1961 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Hintikka, Jaakko
      - "Carnap's Semantics in Retrospect", undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - "Knowledge by Acquaintance Individuation by Acquaintance", undated (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - "Modality and Quantification", 1961 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Hirst, R.J., "R. B. Braithwaite on Science and Ethics", undated (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Hochberg, Herbert
      - "Some Comments on Universals and Particulars", undated (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - "Mapping, Meaning, and Metaphysics", 1974 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Hodges, Michael, "Meaning and the Impotence Hypothesis", 1976 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Hofman, Jim, Notes, undated (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Holmer, Paul L., "The Nature of Theology", 1952 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Holzner, Burkhart
      - "The Concept "Integration" in Sociological Theory", 1965 (Box 70, Folder 18)
      - "Science as a Social Phenomenon", 1965 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Hooker, C.A., "A Divorce between Primary and Secondary Qualities?", 1970 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Hooker, Michael, "Peirce's Conception of Truth", 1968 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Hosler, Douglas
      - "Thoughts as Episodes", 1962 (Box 70, Folder 22)
      - Thesis Draft, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Hospers, John, "Art and Beauty", 1955 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Hoy, Ronald C.
      - "C.D. Broad's Theory of Temporal Experience", 1974 (Box 70, Folder 25)
      - "Cognitive Aspects of Art and Science", 1971 (Box 70, Folder 26)
      - "Dispositions, Logical States, and Mental Occurents", 1977 (Box 70, Folder 27)
      - "The Given and the Self Presenting", 1982 (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Hylton, Peter
      - "The Metaphysics of T. H. Green", undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - "The Nature of the Proposition and the Revolt against Idealism", c.1983 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - "Russell and the Origins of Analytic Philosophy", undated (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - "The Significance of 'On Denoting'", 1980 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Issar, Arie
      - "From the Big Bang to Infinite Intelligence", 1988 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - "The Role of Geology in Understanding the Extension and Meaning of the Dimension of Time", 1980 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - "The Universe as a Field of Order (Negra Entropy) Measured by Space Time Information Dimensions", 1981 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Iyer, K. A. Krishnaswami, "Philosophy of the Advaita", undated (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Jackson, Frank, "On the Adverbial Analysis of Visual Experience", 1975 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Jensen, Henning, "Reid and Wittgenstein on Philosophy and Language", 1978 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Johnson, David M.
      - "Another Perspective on the Speckled Hen", c.1970 (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - "Can Belief Be Commanded?", 1976 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - "A Formulation Model of Perceptual Knowledge", c.1971 (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - "A Non-Traditional Empiricism", 1970 (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - "Time and Kant's 'Monism'", c.1970 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Johnstone, Henry W
      - "Can Philosophical Arguments be Valid?", 1962 (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - "Odysseus as Traveler: A Categorical Study", undated (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Jones, Gary, "On Popper's Philosophy of Science", 1982 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Jonsen, Albert, "A Reinterpretation of Natural Law Ethics", c.1970 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Joseph, Geoffrey, "Special Cases", c.1982 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Juarez-Paz, Rigoberto
      - "Mr. Toulmin on the Meaning of Ethical Terms", 1955 (Box 71, Folder 21)
      - "S.E. Toulmin's Conception of the Place of Reason in Ethics", undated (Box 71, Folder 22)
      - "Vlastos, Sellars, and 'The Third Man'", 1955 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Kahn, Charles H.
      - "Language and Ontology in the Cratylus", 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - "Sensation and Consciousness in Aristotle's Psychology", 1966 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Kane, Robert, "Free Will and Values", 1982 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Kaplan, Abraham, "Logical Empiricism and Value Judgments", 1954 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Kaplan, David
      - "An Essay on the Sematics, Logic, Metaphysics and Epistemology of Demonstratives", 1977 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - "Individuals in Intensional Logic", 1967 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - "Significance and Analyticity", 1959 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - "What is Russell's Theory of Descriptions?", c.1966 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Katz, Aaron, "Toward a Scientific Culture", 1962 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Kearns, John, "Substance and Time", 1969 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Kelly, Richard, "Subjectivity and Objectivity", undated (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Kemeny, John G., "Notes on Reduction", undated (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Kim, Jaegwon, "Concepts of Supervenience", 1983 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Kirk, Robert, "On Three Alleged Rivals to Homophonic Translation", 1981 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Kitcher, Patricia, "Discovering the Forms of Intuition", c.1982 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Kiteley, Murray
      - "Existence and the Ontological", 1955 (Box 72, Folder 16)
      - "The Grammars of 'Believe'", c.1956 (Box 72, Folder 17)
      - "Is Existence Predicate?", c.1960 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Kliger, George, "The Philosophy of Tadeusz Kotarbinski", undated (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Kline, George, "Form, Concrescence, and Concretum: A Neo-Whitteheadian Analysis", 1967 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Kockelmans, Joseph J., "Toward a Transcendental-Ontological Doctrine of Categories: Some Reflections on the Doctrine", c.1978 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Kolb, David, "Sellars and the Measure of all Things", 1975 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Kordig, Carl R., "Inter-Theory Relations: Reference, Self-Reference, Correspondence, Cumulativity, Theory-Ladeness", c.1980 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Krantz, David, "Finding the Appropriate Three-Variable Model", 1965 (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Kraut, Robert
      - "Attitudes and Their Objects", 1978 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - "Demonstratives, Definite Descriptions, and Objects: Some Remarks on Kripke's Theory of Proper Names", c. 1968 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - "Indiscernibility and Ontology", c.1978 (Box 73, Folder 3)